https://www.gordano.com/cookies-and-privacy-policy/

Cookies and how they benefit you
Our website uses cookies, as almost all websites do, to help provide you with the best experience we can. Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer or mobile device when you browse websites.
Our cookies help us:
Make our website work as you would expect
Save you having to log in every time you visit the site
Improve the speed/security of the site
We do not use cookies to:
Collect any personally identifiable information (without your express permission)
Collect any sensitive information (without your express permission)
Pass data to advertising networks
Pass personally identifiable data to third parties
You can learn more about all the cookies we use below.
Granting us permission to use cookies
Two primary factors relate to confirmation of cookie acceptance on our websites:
If the settings on your software that you are using to view this website (your browser) are adjusted to accept cookies
Your continued use of our website following an opt-in acknowledgement during the first visit to our website (or subsequent visits following updates to this cookie policy)
Should you wish to remove or not use cookies from our site you can learn how to do this below, however doing so will likely mean that our site will not work as you would expect.
Cookies in use with our websites and services
We use cookies to make our website work including:
Making our shopping cart and checkout work
Determining if you are logged in or not
Remembering your search settings
Remembering if you have accepted our terms and conditions
There is no way to prevent these cookies being set other than to not use our websites and related services.
Third party functions
Our site (or third party integrated websites), like most websites, includes functionality provided by third parties. Examples of this include:
Embedded videos (e.g.: Vimeo, YouTube)
2Checkout payment processing that happens when you sign up for our Cloud services
Disabling these cookies will likely break the functions offered by these third parties. Please note that third parties (including, for example, advertising networks and providers of external services like web traffic analysis services) may also use cookies, over which we have no control. These cookies are likely to be analytical/performance cookies or targeting cookies.
Anonymous Visitor Statistics Cookies
We use cookies to compile visitor statistics such as how many people have visited our website, what type of technology they are using (e.g. Mac or Windows), which helps to identify when our site isn’t working as it should for particular technologies), how long they spend on the site, what page they look at, etc. This helps us to continuously improve our website. These analytics programs also tell us if, on an anonymous basis, how people reached this site (e.g. from a search engine) and whether they have been here before.
Cookies we use on our own websites:
Cookie
Name
Purpose
Google Analytics
_gat
_gid
_ga
These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited.
WordPress
PHPSESSID
A native PHP cookie that enables serialised stated data. It is used to establish a user session.
Vimeo
vuid
We use Vimeo to embed videos onto our website. These cookies are used by Vimeo to collect analytics tracking information
Turning cookies off
You can typically switch cookies off by adjusting your browser settings to stop it from accepting cookies. Doing so however will likely limit the functionality of our website and a large proportion of the world’s websites as cookies are a standard part of most modern websites.
Our Privacy Policy
Gordano Ltd (we, our, us) are committed to protecting and respecting your privacy.
This policy (together with our terms of use as set out at):
https://www.gordano.com/wp-content/themes/loom/termsConditions/GMS_Cloudline_ToS_2016.pdf (Terms) applies to your use of:
the websites (includes: https://www.gordano.com/ & https://www.gms-cloud.com/) (Websites)
the cloud platform known as GMS Cloud (Platform).
any of the services accessible through the Platform (Services), unless the Terms state that a separate privacy policy applies to a particular Service, in which case that privacy policy only applies.
This policy sets out the basis on which any personal data we collect from you, or that you provide to us, will be processed by us. Please read the following carefully to understand our views and practices regarding your personal data and how we will treat it, and your rights pertaining to that data.
For the purpose of GDPR compliance the data controller is: Gordano Ltd, 1 Yeo Bank Business Park, Kenn Road, Clevedon, North Somerset, BS21 6UW, United Kingdom.
Data processing activities: Information we may collect about you
We may collect and process the following data about you:
Information you give us:
You may give us information about you by filling in forms in the Platform, or by corresponding with us (for example, by email). This includes information you provide when you register a user account, access the Platform, subscribe to any of our Services, share data via the Platform, make use of certain functions within the Platform, submit an enquiry or comment to us and when you report a problem with our Services. The information you give us may include your name, address, email address and phone number, age, username, password and other registration information, financial and credit card information, personal description and photograph. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
Information we collect about you and your device:
Each time you use the Platform and the Websites we may automatically collect the following information:
technical information, including the type of device you use, a unique device identifier, the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect to the Internet, your login information, operating system, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions;
details of your use of our Platform including, but not limited to, traffic data, location data, weblogs and other communication data, and the resources that you access.
Location information:
We may also use various technologies to determine your current location.
Information we receive from other sources:
In the course of providing Services to you we may use data from third parties to ensure the correct level of Service delivery, including, for example, confirming contact information via LinkedIn or other publicly accessible business data repositories. Similarly, we may receive data from technology partners (e.g.: payment processing companies integrated with our Services) to ensure adequate contact options are available to confirm Service subscription parameters and usage.
Legal basis for processing your dataÂ
We may process your data because:
we are legally obliged to e.g. to confirm your identity;
the processing is necessary for the performance of the contract with you to provide the Services; or
it is in our legitimate business interests to do so.
In some instances, we will rely on your consent to process personal data and where we do this, it will be flagged to you at the time.
We retain personal information that you provide to us where we have a legitimate business need to do so (for example, as long as is required in order to complete a sale, maintain access to the Platform, provide support services). Where we no longer have a legitimate business need to process your personal information, we securely delete the information or anonymise it.
The provision of personal data by the Website, Service and Platform users is necessary to satisfy the contractual requirements of using the Service, i.e.: certain pieces of personal information are necessary to permit usage of and maintain access to the Service, e.g.: where payment processing is required to start or continue using the Service. Failure to provide this information may result in incomplete Service onboarding and thus an inability to use the Service and related services.
Uses made of the information (the purpose)
In addition to the general provision of the Services, and the specific uses of information we describe in this policy, we may use information held about you in the following ways:
to remember your user account information, preferences and settings so that you will not have re-enter them each time you access and use the Services
to help you access your information and account settings after you have signed into your user account
to identify you and manage any accounts you hold with us
to carry out our obligations arising from contracts between us (including processing orders, invoicing, providing support)
to provide customised and personalised content and information to you
to enable us to provide, test, improve and update our Services and monitor the performance and effectiveness of the Services and specific functionalities
to enable us to develop and test new products, services and features
to enable us to identify, diagnose and fix any defects or errors
for monitoring purposes, including metrics data
to provide you with information about other goods and services we offer that are similar to the Services
to provide you, or permit selected third parties to provide you, with information about other goods or services we feel may interest you
We may associate any category of information with any other category of information and will treat the combined information as personal data in accordance with this policy for as long as it is combined.
Disclosure of your information
We may disclose your personal information to any member of our group, which means our parent company: Innovation Technology Investments.
We may disclose your personal information to third parties:
in the event that we sell or buy any business or assets, in which case we may disclose your personal data to the prospective seller or buyer of such business or assets
if we are under a duty to disclose or share your personal data in order to comply with any legal or regulatory obligation or request
who help us provide the Services to you
who you interact with via the Services and/or confirm that you wish to be contacted by
in order to:
enforce or apply our Terms and other agreements or to investigate potential breaches; or
protect the rights, property or safety of Gordano Ltd, our customers, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organisations for the purposes of fraud protection and credit risk reduction.
Where we store your personal data
The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, a destination outside the European Economic Area (EEA), including services provided by companies such as Freshsales (CRM), Atlassian (Issue tracking and project management), Zoom.us (voice and video conferencing). It may also be processed by staff operating outside the EEA who work for us or for one of our suppliers. These staff may be engaged in the fulfilment of your request, order or reservation, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services. By submitting your personal data, you agree to this transfer, storing or processing. We will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this privacy policy.
Whenever we send data to countries that do not enjoy the same type of protection as General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR), we only do so if appropriate safeguards are in place in accordance with the requirements of GDPR.
All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password that enables you to access certain parts of the Services, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share a password with anyone.
Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your personal data, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our Platform or via any other Service; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access.
We may collect and store personal data on your devices using data caches and browser web storage (including HTML 5) and other technology.
How long do we keep your personal information?
We keep your personal information for as long as we need to for the purposes for which it was collected or (if longer) for any period for which we are required to keep personal information to comply with our legal and regulatory requirements.
Your rights
You have the right to ask us not to process your personal data for marketing purposes. We will usually inform you (before collecting your data) if we intend to use your data for such purposes or if we intend to disclose your information to any third party for such purposes. You can exercise your right to prevent such processing by contacting us at privacy@gordano.com.
You can also ask us to update, correct or delete your data. If we are relying on consent, you can withdraw your consent to our processing of your personal data (including any direct marketing). If we are relying on legitimate interests for direct marketing, you can object to receiving such direct marketing. You may lodge a complaint with the UK supervisory body, the Information Commissionerâ€™s Office (the ICO) here https://ico.org.uk/. If you have a concern or complaint about the way we handle your data, we ask that you contact us in the first instance to allow us to investigate and resolve the matter as appropriate.
Our Services may, from time to time, contain links to and from the websites of our partner networks, advertisers and affiliates. If you follow a link to any of these websites, please note that these websites and any services that may be accessible through them have their own privacy policies and that we do not accept any responsibility or liability for these policies or for any personal data that may be collected through these websites or services, such as contact and location data. Please check these policies before you submit any personal data to these websites or use these services.
Access to information
The General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) gives you the right to access information held about you. Your right of access can be exercised in accordance with GDPR. We maintain a formal Subject Access Request (SAR) policy to manage requests of this type. SARs are required to be submitted in writing via email (to privacy@gordano.com) or physical media (a letter â€“ to the address listed above). Upon receipt of the SAR additional information may be requested to validate the identity of the SAR requester, or to contextualise or otherwise assist with the SAR. You will not normally be charged for a SAR except in certain circumstances where the SAR is manifestly unfounded, excessive or repetitive.
Changes to this privacy policy
Any changes we may make to our privacy policy in the future will be posted on this page and, where appropriate permission is active, notified to you by email, or when you next access the Platform and Websites. The new terms will be displayed on-screen and you will be required to read and accept them to continue your use of the Websites, the Platform or the Services.
Contact
Questions, comments and requests regarding this privacy policy are welcomed and should be addressed to privacy@gordano.com, using the email subject line: Query about Gordano Privacy Policy.
We use cookies to ensure that we give you the best experience on our website. If you continue to use this site we will assume that you are happy with it.OkRead more
